Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/addison-moore

Github: github.com/addison912
Website: addisonmoore.me
Phone: (510) 333-5490

I'm a data consultant and software engineer from the San Francisco Bay Area with 9+ years of experience working in tech. Over the past five years, I've worked with dozens of enterprise clients and gained experience with a variety of tools and languages to help my clients find value in their data.

## **SKILLS**

Languages: Python, Javascript/Typescript, HTML, CSS, Bash, French

Data: Tableau, Power BI, Pandas, Snowflake, GCP, DBT, Jupyter, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Apache Airflow

Frameworks and Libraries: React, React-Native, Next.js, Flask, Django

Server: Python, Node.js, Express, Linux, Docker, NGINX, restful APIs, Proxmox, VMs

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Self-employed / Data Analyst, Full Stack Software Engineer

MAY 2023 - December 2024, SAN FRANCISCO

- Used data analytics to identify inefficiencies in a futures market. Used Python to analyze datasets and optimize trading strategies.
- Created a full stack application and database to ingest and analyze market data, and automate trading strategies.
- Traded over 2 million contracts and achieved over \$70k in quarterly profits prior to the market closing in December of 2024.

# Stratus Data / Data Science Consultant, Software Engineer

September 2021 - APRIL 2023, SAN FRANCISCO / REMOTE

- Developed efficient data pipelines using SQL, Python, DBT, and Snowflake for Nasco Healthcare. Created data visualizations to identify supply chain bottlenecks and increase monthly OTIF (on time in full) shipments by over 20%.
- Conducted data analysis and created visualizations for Hancock Askew & Co. Provided insights into the profitability of employees, branches, and regions. Completed staffing analysis and visualizations to support the creation of a staffing plan designed to save \$200k in overtime pay during tax season.
- Scraped millions of manually written invoices using Python, regex, and natural language processing for The Miner Corporation.
   Identified core products and created a new standardized parts catalog to save sales representatives thousands of hours annually.
- Analyzed millions of outreach messages for CareMessage from community healthcare centers using Python and natural language processing. Identified trends in outreach response rates and created a messaging guide to increase response rates by up to 30%
- As the sole full stack engineer at Stratus Data, I built and launched Stratus Apps, a client-facing web portal. I also worked on several
  internal tools to improve the efficacy of operations and to enable data scientists to launch client-facing dashboards.

#### Quantum Metric / Customer Success Engineer

JULY 2019 - JULY 2020, SAN FRANCISCO / REMOTE

- Primary customer success engineer servicing over \$5M in contracts for brands such as Stubhub, Western Union, eBay, Lululemon, CSAA Insurance and more.
- Created data visualizations, met daily with stakeholders, and presented findings at QBRs.
- Hosted regular on-site events and led trainings.
- Helped account executives generate leads and increase contracts with existing clients by introducing new teams to our product.
- Wrote clean and readable code to gather analytics data and help brands measure their KPIs.

## The Bosco / Product Designer

JUNE 2015 - OCTOBER 2018, SAN FRANCISCO

- Lead designer on new core products generating over \$10M in revenue, including The Bosco Lite and The Bosco Multicam.
- Launched The Bosco's San Francisco office. Hired and managed a team of 6 staff members.

# **EDUCATION**

#### **General Assembly**

NOVEMBER 2018 - FEBRUARY 2019. SAN FRANCISCO

Software Engineering Immersive - 4 month full-time program

California State University of Monterey Bay - Bachelor of Arts - Visual and Public Art, with a concentration in Digital Art and 3D Design Online certificates and courses:

- University of Michigan: Python Data Structures.
- Frontend Masters: Intermediate React, Typescript, Git In-Depth, Production-Grade TypeScript, Networking and Streams.
- Coursera: Meta Backend Certificate, Game Programming with C#.